<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MOMO</string>

    <!--
    <string name="terms_of_service">서비스약관</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">개인정보</string>
    -->

    <string name="terms_of_service">
        제 1장 총칙\n\n

제 1조 (목적)\n
\n
이 약관은 “MOMO”(이하 “회사”라 합니다)가 제공하는 “MOMO 앱 서비스”(이하 \'서비스\'라 합니다)를 회사와 이용계약을 체결한 \'고객\'이 이용함에 있어 필요한 회사와 고객의 권리 및 의무, 기타 제반 사항을 정함을 목적으로 합니다.\n
\n
제 2조 (약관 외 준칙)\n
\n
이 약관에 명시되지 않은 사항에 대해서는 위치 정보의 보호 및 이용 등에 관한 법률, 전기통신사업법, 정보통신망 이용 촉진및 보호 등에 관한 법률 등 관계법령 및 회사가 정한 서비스의 세부이용지침 등의 규정에 따릅니다.\n
\n
제 2장 서비스의 이용\n
\n
제 3조 (가입자격)\n
\n
① 서비스에 가입할 수 있는 자는 Application 이 설치가능한 모든 사람 입니다.\n
\n
제 4조 (서비스 가입)\n
\n
① “Application 관리자”가 정한 본 약관에 고객이 동의하면 서비스 가입의 효력이 발생합니다.\n
\n
② “Application 관리자”는 다음 각 호의 고객 가입신청에 대해서는 이를 승낙하지 아니할 수 있습니다.\n
\n
1. 고객 등록 사항을 누락하거나 오기하여 신청하는 경우\n
\n
2. 공공질서 또는 미풍양속을 저해하거나 저해할 목적으로 신청한 경우\n
\n
3. 기타 회사가 정한 이용신청 요건이 충족되지 않았을 경우\n
\n
제 5조 (서비스의 탈퇴)\n
\n
서비스 탈퇴를 희망하는 고객은 “Application 담당자”가 정한 소정의 절차(설정메뉴의 탈퇴)를 통해 서비스 해지를 신청할 수 있습니다.\n
\n
제 6조 (서비스의 수준)\n
\n
① 서비스의 이용은 연중무휴 1일 24시간을 원칙으로 합니다. 단, 회사의 업무상이나 기술상의 이유로 서비스가 일시 중지될 수 있으며, 운영상의 목적으로 회사가 정한 기간에는 서비스가 일시 중지될 수 있습니다. 이러한 경우 회사는 사전 또는 사후에 이를 공지합니다.\n
\n
② 위치정보는 관련 기술의 발전에 따라 오차가 발생할 수 있습니다.\n
\n
제 7조 (서비스 이용의 제한 및 정지)\n
\n
회사는 고객이 다음 각 호에 해당하는 경우 사전 통지 없이 고객의 서비스 이용을 제한 또는 정지하거나 직권 해지를 할 수 있습니다.\n
\n
1. 타인의 서비스 이용을 방해하거나 타인의 개인정보를 도용한 경우\n
\n
2. 서비스를 이용하여 법령, 공공질서, 미풍양속 등에 반하는 행위를 한 경우\n
\n
제 8조 (서비스의 변경 및 중지)\n
\n
① 회사는 다음 각 호의 1에 해당하는 경우 고객에게 서비스의 전부 또는 일부를 제한, 변경하거나 중지할 수 있습니다.\n
\n
1. 서비스용 설비의 보수 등 공사로 인한 부득이한 경우\n
\n
2. 정전, 제반 설비의 장애 또는 이용량의 폭주 등으로 정상적인 서비스 이용에 지장이 있는 경우\n
\n
3. 서비스 제휴업체와의 계약 종료 등과 같은 회사의 제반 사정 또는 법률상의 장애 등으로 서비스를 유지할 수 없는 경우\n
\n
4.기타 천재지변, 국가비상사태 등 불가항력적 사유가 있는 경우\n
\n
② 제1항에 의한 서비스 중단의 경우에는 회사는 인터넷 등에 공지하거나 고객에게 통지합니다. 다만, 회사가 통제할 수 없는 사유로 인한 서비스의 중단 (운영자의 고의, 과실이 없는 디스크 장애, 시스템 다운 등)으로 인하여 사전 통지가 불가능한 경우에는 사후에 통지합니다.\n
\n\n
제 5장 기타\n
\n
제 19조 (회사의 연락처)\n
\n
회사의 상호 다음과 같습니다.\n
\n
1. 상호: “MOMO”\n
\n
1. 이메일 주소: momoisdiary@gmail.com\n
\n
제 20조 (양도금지)\n
\n
고객 및 회사는 고객의 서비스 가입에 따른 본 약관상의 지위 또는 권리,의무의 전부 또는 일부를 제3자에게 양도, 위임하거나 담보제공 등의 목적으로 처분할 수 없습니다.\n
\n
제 21조 (손해배상)\n
\n
① 고객의 고의나 과실에 의해 이 약관의 규정을 위반함으로 인하여 회사에 손해가 발생하게 되는 경우, 이 약관을 위반한 고객은 회사에 발생하는 모든 손해를 배상하여야 합니다.\n
\n
② 고객이 서비스를 이용함에 있어 행한 불법행위나 고객의 고의나 과실에 의해 이 약관 위반행위로 인하여 회사가 당해 고객 이외의 제3자로부터 손해배상청구 또는 소송을 비롯한 각종 이의제기를 받는 경우 당해 고객은 그로 인하여 회사에 발생한 손해를 배상하여야 합니다.\n
\n
③ 회사가 위치정보의 보호 및 이용 등에 관한 법률 제 15조 내지 제26조의 규정을 위반한 행위 혹은 회사가 제공하는 서비스로 인하여 고객에게 손해가 발생한 경우, 회사가 고의 또는 과실 없음을 입증하지 아니하면, 고객의 손해에 대하여 책임을 부담합니다.\n
\n
제 22조 (면책사항)\n
\n
① 회사는 천재지변 또는 이에 준하는 불가항력으로 인하여 서비스를 제공할 수 없는 경우에는 서비스 제공에 관한 책임이 면제됩니다.\n
\n
② 회사는 고객의 귀책사유로 인한 서비스의 이용장애에 대하여 책임을 지지 않습니다.\n
\n
③ 회사는 고객이 서비스를 이용하여 기대하는 수익을 상실한 것에 대하여 책임을 지지 않으며, 그 밖에 서비스를 통하여 얻은 자료로 인한 손해 등에 대하여도 책임을 지지 않습니다.\n
\n
④ 회사에서 제공하는 서비스 및 서비스를 이용하여 얻은 정보에 대한 최종판단은 고객이 직접 하여야 하고, 그에 따른 책임은 전적으로 고객 자신에게 있으며, 회사는 그로 인하여 발생하는 손해에 대해서 책임을 부담하지 않습니다.\n
\n
⑤ 회사의 업무상 또는 기술상의 장애로 인하여 서비스를 개시하지 못하는 경우 회사는 인터넷 홈페이지 등에 이를 공지하거나 E-mail 등의 방법으로 고객에게 통지합니다. 단, 회사가 통제할 수 없는 사유로 인하여 사전 공지가 불가능한 경우에는 사후에 공지합니다.\n
\n
제 23조 (분쟁의 해결 및 관할법원)\n
\n
① 서비스 이용과 관련하여 회사와 고객 사이에 분쟁이 발생한 경우, 회사와 고객은 분쟁의 해결을 위해 성실히 협의합니다.\n
\n
② 제1항의 협의에서도 분쟁이 해결되지 않을 경우 양 당사자는 정보통신망 이용촉진 및 정보보호 등에 관한 법률 제33조의 규정에 의한 개인정보분쟁조정위원회에 분쟁조정을 신청할 수 있습니다.\n
    </string>


    <string name="privacy_policy">
    1. 개인정보의 처리 목적 (\'https://blog.naver.com/heey1792\'이하 \'MOMO\') 은(는) 다음의 목적을 위하여 개인정보를 처리하고 있으며, 다음의 목적 이외의 용도로는 이용하지 않습니다.\n
\n
- 고객 가입의사 확인, 고객에 대한 서비스 제공에 따른 본인 식별.인증, 회원자격 유지.관리, 물품 또는 서비스 공급에 따른 금액 결제, 물품 또는 서비스의 공급.배송 등\n
\n
2. 개인정보의 처리 및 보유 기간\n
\n
① (\'https://blog.naver.com/heey1792\'이하 \'MOMO\') 은(는) 정보주체로부터 개인정보를 수집할 때 동의 받은 개인정보 보유․이용기간 또는 법령에 따른 개인정보 보유․이용기간 내에서 개인정보를 처리․보유합니다.\n
\n
② 구체적인 개인정보 처리 및 보유 기간은 다음과 같습니다.\n
\n
☞ 아래 예시를 참고하여 개인정보 처리업무와 개인정보 처리업무에 대한 보유기간 및 관련 법령, 근거 등을 기재합니다.\n
\n
(예시)- 고객 가입 및 관리 : 서비스 이용계약 또는 회원가입 해지시까지, 다만 채권․채무관계 잔존시에는 해당 채권․채무관계 정산시까지\n
\n
- 전자상거래에서의 계약․청약철회, 대금결제, 재화 등 공급기록 : 5년\n
3. 정보주체와 법정대리인의 권리·의무 및 그 행사방법 이용자는 개인정보주체로써 다음과 같은 권리를 행사할 수 있습니다.\n
\n
① 정보주체는 MOMO(\'https://blog.naver.com/heey1792\'이하 \'MOMO) 에 대해 언제든지 다음 각 호의 개인정보 보호 관련 권리를 행사할 수 있습니다.\n
\n
1. 개인정보 열람요구\n
\n
2. 오류 등이 있을 경우 정정 요구\n
\n
3. 삭제요구\n
\n
4. 처리정지 요구\n
\n
\n
4. 처리하는 개인정보의 항목 작성\n
\n
① (\'https://blog.naver.com/heey1792\'이하 \'MOMO\')은(는) 다음의 개인정보 항목을 처리하고 있습니다.\n
\n
\n

5. 개인정보의 파기(\'MOMO\')은(는) 원칙적으로 개인정보 처리목적이 달성된 경우에는 지체없이 해당 개인정보를 파기합니다. 파기의 절차, 기한 및 방법은 다음과 같습니다.\n
\n
-파기절차\n
이용자가 입력한 정보는 목적 달성 후 별도의 DB에 옮겨져(종이의 경우 별도의 서류) 내부 방침 및 기타 관련 법령에 따라 일정기간 저장된 후 혹은 즉시 파기됩니다. 이 때, DB로 옮겨진 개인정보는 법률에 의한 경우가 아니고서는 다른 목적으로 이용되지 않습니다.\n
\n
-파기기한\n
이용자의 개인정보는 개인정보의 보유기간이 경과된 경우에는 보유기간의 종료일로부터 5일 이내에, 개인정보의 처리 목적 달성, 해당 서비스의 폐지, 사업의 종료 등 그 개인정보가 불필요하게 되었을 때에는 개인정보의 처리가 불필요한 것으로 인정되는 날로부터 5일 이내에 그 개인정보를 파기합니다.\n
\n
\n

6. 개인정보 자동 수집 장치의 설치•운영 및 거부에 관한 사항\n
\n
MOMO 은 정보주체의 이용정보를 저장하고 수시로 불러오는 \'쿠키\'를 사용하지 않습니다.\n
\n
7. 개인정보 보호책임자 작성\n
\n
① MOMO(\'https://blog.naver.com/heey1792\'이하 MOMO) 은(는) 개인정보 처리에 관한 업무를 총괄해서 책임지고, 개인정보 처리와 관련한 정보주체의 불만처리 및 피해구제 등을 위하여 아래와 같이 개인정보 보호책임자를 지정하고 있습니다.\n
\n
▶ 개인정보 보호책임자\n
성명 :김희영\n
직책 :매니저\n
직급 :매니저\n
연락처 :01052356510, momoisdiary@gmail.com,\n
※ 개인정보 보호 담당부서로 연결됩니다.\n
\n
▶ 개인정보 보호 담당부서\n
부서명 :\n
담당자 :\n
연락처 :, ,\n
② 정보주체께서는 MOMO(\'https://blog.naver.com/heey1792\'이하 MOMO) 의 서비스(또는 사업)을 이용하시면서 발생한 모든 개인정보 보호 관련 문의, 불만처리, 피해구제 등에 관한 사항을 개인정보 보호책임자 및 담당부서로 문의하실 수 있습니다. MOMO(\'https://blog.naver.com/heey1792\'이하 \'MOMO) 은(는) 정보주체의 문의에 대해 지체 없이 답변 및 처리해드릴 것입니다.\n
\n
8. 개인정보 처리방침 변경\n
\n
①이 개인정보처리방침은 시행일로부터 적용되며, 법령 및 방침에 따른 변경내용의 추가, 삭제 및 정정이 있는 경우에는 변경사항의 시행 7일 전부터 공지사항을 통하여 고지할 것입니다.\n
\n
\n

9. 개인정보의 안전성 확보 조치 (\'MOMO\')은(는) 개인정보보호법 제29조에 따라 다음과 같이 안전성 확보에 필요한 기술적/관리적 및 물리적 조치를 하고 있습니다.\n
\n
1. 해킹 등에 대비한 기술적 대책\n
&lt;MOMO&gt;(\'MOMO\')은 해킹이나 컴퓨터 바이러스 등에 의한 개인정보 유출 및 훼손을 막기 위하여 보안프로그램을 설치하고 주기적인 갱신·점검을 하며 외부로부터 접근이 통제된 구역에 시스템을 설치하고 기술적/물리적으로 감시 및 차단하고 있습니다.\n
\n
2. 개인정보의 암호화\n
이용자의 개인정보는 비밀번호는 암호화 되어 저장 및 관리되고 있어, 본인만이 알 수 있으며 중요한 데이터는 파일 및 전송 데이터를 암호화 하거나 파일 잠금 기능을 사용하는 등의 별도 보안기능을 사용하고 있습니다.\n
\n
3. 개인정보에 대한 접근 제한\n
개인정보를 처리하는 데이터베이스시스템에 대한 접근권한의 부여,변경,말소를 통하여 개인정보에 대한 접근통제를 위하여 필요한 조치를 하고 있으며 침입차단시스템을 이용하여 외부로부터의 무단 접근을 통제하고 있습니다.\n
\n
\n
    </string>

    <string name="apache_license">
        Apache License\n
\n
Version 2.0, January 2004\n
\n
http://www.apache.org/licenses/\n
\n
TERMS AND CONDITIONS FOR USE, REPRODUCTION, AND DISTRIBUTION\n
\n
1. Definitions.\n
\n
"License" shall mean the terms and conditions for use, reproduction, and distribution as defined by Sections 1 through 9 of this document.\n
\n
"Licensor" shall mean the copyright owner or entity authorized by the copyright owner that is granting the License.\n
\n
"Legal Entity" shall mean the union of the acting entity and all other entities that control, are controlled by, or are under common control with that entity. For the purposes of this definition, "control" means (i) the power, direct or indirect, to cause the direction or management of such entity, whether by contract or otherwise, or (ii) ownership of fifty percent (50%) or more of the outstanding shares, or (iii) beneficial ownership of such entity.\n
\n
"You" (or "Your") shall mean an individual or Legal Entity exercising permissions granted by this License.\n
\n
"Source" form shall mean the preferred form for making modifications, including but not limited to software source code, documentation source, and configuration files.\n
\n
"Object" form shall mean any form resulting from mechanical transformation or translation of a Source form, including but not limited to compiled object code, generated documentation, and conversions to other media types.\n
\n
"Work" shall mean the work of authorship, whether in Source or Object form, made available under the License, as indicated by a copyright notice that is included in or attached to the work (an example is provided in the Appendix below).\n
\n
"Derivative Works" shall mean any work, whether in Source or Object form, that is based on (or derived from) the Work and for which the editorial revisions, annotations, elaborations, or other modifications represent, as a whole, an original work of authorship. For the purposes of this License, Derivative Works shall not include works that remain separable from, or merely link (or bind by name) to the interfaces of, the Work and Derivative Works thereof.\n
\n
"Contribution" shall mean any work of authorship, including the original version of the Work and any modifications or additions to that Work or Derivative Works thereof, that is intentionally submitted to Licensor for inclusion in the Work by the copyright owner or by an individual or Legal Entity authorized to submit on behalf of the copyright owner. For the purposes of this definition, "submitted" means any form of electronic, verbal, or written communication sent to the Licensor or its representatives, including but not limited to communication on electronic mailing lists, source code control systems, and issue tracking systems that are managed by, or on behalf of, the Licensor for the purpose of discussing and improving the Work, but excluding communication that is conspicuously marked or otherwise designated in writing by the copyright owner as "Not a Contribution."\n
\n
"Contributor" shall mean Licensor and any individual or Legal Entity on behalf of whom a Contribution has been received by Licensor and subsequently incorporated within the Work.\n
\n
2. Grant of Copyright License. Subject to the terms and conditions of this License, each Contributor hereby grants to You a perpetual, worldwide, non-exclusive, no-charge, royalty-free, irrevocable copyright license to reproduce, prepare Derivative Works of, publicly display, publicly perform, sublicense, and distribute the Work and such Derivative Works in Source or Object form.\n
\n
3. Grant of Patent License. Subject to the terms and conditions of this License, each Contributor hereby grants to You a perpetual, worldwide, non-exclusive, no-charge, royalty-free, irrevocable (except as stated in this section) patent license to make, have made, use, offer to sell, sell, import, and otherwise transfer the Work, where such license applies only to those patent claims licensable by such Contributor that are necessarily infringed by their Contribution(s) alone or by combination of their Contribution(s) with the Work to which such Contribution(s) was submitted. If You institute patent litigation against any entity (including a cross-claim or counterclaim in a lawsuit) alleging that the Work or a Contribution incorporated within the Work constitutes direct or contributory patent infringement, then any patent licenses granted to You under this License for that Work shall terminate as of the date such litigation is filed.\n
\n
4. Redistribution. You may reproduce and distribute copies of the Work or Derivative Works thereof in any medium, with or without modifications, and in Source or Object form, provided that You meet the following conditions:\n
\n
You must give any other recipients of the Work or Derivative Works a copy of this License; and\n
You must cause any modified files to carry prominent notices stating that You changed the files; and\n
You must retain, in the Source form of any Derivative Works that You distribute, all copyright, patent, trademark, and attribution notices from the Source form of the Work, excluding those notices that do not pertain to any part of the Derivative Works; and
If the Work includes a "NOTICE" text file as part of its distribution, then any Derivative Works that You distribute must include a readable copy of the attribution notices contained within such NOTICE file, excluding those notices that do not pertain to any part of the Derivative Works, in at least one of the following places: within a NOTICE text file distributed as part of the Derivative Works; within the Source form or documentation, if provided along with the Derivative Works; or, within a display generated by the Derivative Works, if and wherever such third-party notices normally appear. The contents of the NOTICE file are for informational purposes only and do not modify the License. You may add Your own attribution notices within Derivative Works that You distribute, alongside or as an addendum to the NOTICE text from the Work, provided that such additional attribution notices cannot be construed as modifying the License.\n
\n
You may add Your own copyright statement to Your modifications and may provide additional or different license terms and conditions for use, reproduction, or distribution of Your modifications, or for any such Derivative Works as a whole, provided Your use, reproduction, and distribution of the Work otherwise complies with the conditions stated in this License.\n
5. Submission of Contributions. Unless You explicitly state otherwise, any Contribution intentionally submitted for inclusion in the Work by You to the Licensor shall be under the terms and conditions of this License, without any additional terms or conditions. Notwithstanding the above, nothing herein shall supersede or modify the terms of any separate license agreement you may have executed with Licensor regarding such Contributions.\n
\n
6. Trademarks. This License does not grant permission to use the trade names, trademarks, service marks, or product names of the Licensor, except as required for reasonable and customary use in describing the origin of the Work and reproducing the content of the NOTICE file.\n
\n
7. Disclaimer of Warranty. Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, Licensor provides the Work (and each Contributor provides its Contributions) on an "AS IS" BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied, including, without limitation, any warranties or conditions of TITLE, NON-INFRINGEMENT, MERCHANTABILITY, or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. You are solely responsible for determining the appropriateness of using or redistributing the Work and assume any risks associated with Your exercise of permissions under this License.\n
\n
8. Limitation of Liability. In no event and under no legal theory, whether in tort (including negligence), contract, or otherwise, unless required by applicable law (such as deliberate and grossly negligent acts) or agreed to in writing, shall any Contributor be liable to You for damages, including any direct, indirect, special, incidental, or consequential damages of any character arising as a result of this License or out of the use or inability to use the Work (including but not limited to damages for loss of goodwill, work stoppage, computer failure or malfunction, or any and all other commercial damages or losses), even if such Contributor has been advised of the possibility of such damages.\n
\n
9. Accepting Warranty or Additional Liability. While redistributing the Work or Derivative Works thereof, You may choose to offer, and charge a fee for, acceptance of support, warranty, indemnity, or other liability obligations and/or rights consistent with this License. However, in accepting such obligations, You may act only on Your own behalf and on Your sole responsibility, not on behalf of any other Contributor, and only if You agree to indemnify, defend, and hold each Contributor harmless for any liability incurred by, or claims asserted against, such Contributor by reason of your accepting any such warranty or additional liability.\n
\n
END OF TERMS AND CONDITIONS\n
    </string>


    <string name="retrofit">
        Copyright 2013 Square, Inc.

Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
You may obtain a copy of the License at

   http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
limitations under the License.
    </string>

    <string name="gson">
        Copyright 2008 Google Inc.

Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
You may obtain a copy of the License at

    http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
limitations under the License.
    </string>

    <string name="image_part_blur">
         Copyright 2016 Tu Yimin (http://github.com/mmin18)

   Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
   you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
   You may obtain a copy of the License at

       http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

   Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
   distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
   WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
   See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
   limitations under the License.
    </string>

    <string name="vertical_seek_bar">
        Copyright (C) 2015 Haruki Hasegawa

Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
You may obtain a copy of the License at

    http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
limitations under the License.
    </string>

    <string name="lottie">
        Copyright 2018 Airbnb, Inc.

   Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
   you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
   You may obtain a copy of the License at

       http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

   Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
   distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
   WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
   See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
   limitations under the License.
    </string>

    <string name="shadow">
        Copyright 2020 SOUP

Licensed to the Apache Software Foundation (ASF) under one or more contributor
license agreements. See the NOTICE file distributed with this work for
additional information regarding copyright ownership. The ASF licenses this
file to you under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License"); you may not
use this file except in compliance with the License. You may obtain a copy of
the License at

   http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS, WITHOUT
WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied. See the
License for the specific language governing permissions and limitations under
the License.
    </string>

    <string name="kotlin">
         Copyright 2000-2020 JetBrains s.r.o. and Kotlin Programming Language contributors.

   Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
   you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
   You may obtain a copy of the License at

       http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

   Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
   distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
   WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
   See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
   limitations under the License.
    </string>

    <string name="glide">
        License for everything not in third_party and not otherwise marked:

Copyright 2014 Google, Inc. All rights reserved.

Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification, are
permitted provided that the following conditions are met:

   1. Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright notice, this list of
         conditions and the following disclaimer.

   2. Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright notice, this list
         of conditions and the following disclaimer in the documentation and/or other materials
         provided with the distribution.

THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY GOOGLE, INC. \'\'AS IS\'\' AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED
WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND
FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL GOOGLE, INC. OR
CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR
CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR
SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON
ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING
NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF
ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.

The views and conclusions contained in the software and documentation are those of the
authors and should not be interpreted as representing official policies, either expressed
or implied, of Google, Inc.
---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
License for third_party/disklrucache:

Copyright 2012 Jake Wharton
Copyright 2011 The Android Open Source Project

Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
You may obtain a copy of the License at

   http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
limitations under the License.
---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
License for third_party/gif_decoder:

Copyright (c) 2013 Xcellent Creations, Inc.

Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining
a copy of this software and associated documentation files (the
"Software"), to deal in the Software without restriction, including
without limitation the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish,
distribute, sublicense, and/or sell copies of the Software, and to
permit persons to whom the Software is furnished to do so, subject to
the following conditions:

The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be
included in all copies or substantial portions of the Software.

THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND,
EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF
MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND
NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE
LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION
OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM, OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION
WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE SOFTWARE.
---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
License for third_party/gif_encoder/AnimatedGifEncoder.java and
third_party/gif_encoder/LZWEncoder.java:

No copyright asserted on the source code of this class. May be used for any
purpose, however, refer to the Unisys LZW patent for restrictions on use of
the associated LZWEncoder class. Please forward any corrections to
kweiner@fmsware.com.

-----------------------------------------------------------------------------
License for third_party/gif_encoder/NeuQuant.java

Copyright (c) 1994 Anthony Dekker

NEUQUANT Neural-Net quantization algorithm by Anthony Dekker, 1994. See
"Kohonen neural networks for optimal colour quantization" in "Network:
Computation in Neural Systems" Vol. 5 (1994) pp 351-367. for a discussion of
the algorithm.

Any party obtaining a copy of these files from the author, directly or
indirectly, is granted, free of charge, a full and unrestricted irrevocable,
world-wide, paid up, royalty-free, nonexclusive right and license to deal in
this software and documentation files (the "Software"), including without
limitation the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute,
sublicense, and/or sell copies of the Software, and to permit persons who
receive copies from any such party to do so, with the only requirement being
that this copyright notice remain intact.
    </string>
</resources>